[
	{
		"question": "The classic 1877 novel \"Black Beauty\" is about what kind of animal?",
		"answer": "Horse",
		"options": ["Horse", "Dog", "Cat", "Rabbit"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How long is an Olympic swimming pool (in meters)?",
		"answer": "50",
		"options": ["50", "100", "75", "25"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which horror author penned the apocalyptic novel \"The Stand\"?",
		"answer": "Stephen King",
		"options": [
			"Stephen King",
			"Bram Stoker",
			"Shirley Jackson",
			"Clive Barker"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which book about a band of rabbits became a bestseller in 1972?",
		"answer": "Watership Down",
		"options": [
			"Watership Down",
			"The Book Thief",
			"Vagabonding",
			"On the Road"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was the first author to use a typewriter in writing a manuscript?",
		"answer": "Mark Twain",
		"options": ["Mark Twain", "Dr. Seuss", "Jane Austen", "Edgar Allan Poe"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which mystery writer holds the Guinness World Record for the most translated works?",
		"answer": "Agatha Christie",
		"options": [
			"Agatha Christie",
			"Arthur Conan Doyle",
			"Dorothy L. Sayers",
			"Stephen King"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was the first president to visit all 50 states?",
		"answer": "Richard Nixon",
		"options": [
			"Richard Nixon",
			"John F. Kennedy",
			"Theodore Roosevelt",
			"Dwight D. Eisenhower"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was the youngest U.S. president?",
		"answer": "Theodore Roosevelt",
		"options": [
			"Theodore Roosevelt",
			"Bill Clinton",
			"John F. Kennedy",
			"Barack Obama"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "What was America's first national park?",
		"answer": "Yellowstone",
		"options": ["Yellowstone", "Zion", "Yosemite", "Grand Canyon"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many floors does the Eiffel Tower have?",
		"answer": "3",
		"options": ["3", "7", "5", "2"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which country produces the most tea?",
		"answer": "China",
		"options": ["China", "Great Britain", "India", "America"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which country do cities of Perth, Adelaide, and Brisbane belong to?",
		"answer": "Australia",
		"options": ["Australia", "Greece", "America", "England"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is \"cynophobia\"?",
		"answer": "fear of dogs",
		"options": [
			"fear of dogs",
			"fear of cars",
			"fear of the dark",
			"fear of horses"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "Who named the Pacific Ocean?",
		"answer": "Ferdinand Magellan",
		"options": [
			"Ferdinand Magellan",
			"Vasco de Balboa",
			"Francisco de Coronado",
			"John Smith"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many languages are written from right to left?",
		"answer": "12",
		"options": ["12", "10", "20", "2"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the name of the biggest technology company in South Korea?",
		"answer": "Samsung",
		"options": ["Samsung", "LG", "Hyundai", "Air Mekong"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which monarch officially made Valentine's Day a holiday in 1537?",
		"answer": "King Henry VIII",
		"options": [
			"King Henry VIII",
			"Queen Victoria",
			"Queen Elizabeth I",
			"King Henry V"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the name of the World's largest ocean?",
		"answer": "Pacific Ocean",
		"options": [
			"Pacific Ocean",
			"Atlantic Ocean",
			"Indian Ocean",
			"Arctic Ocean"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was the first woman pilot to fly solo across the Atlantic?",
		"answer": "Amelia Earhart",
		"options": [
			"Amelia Earhart",
			"Betty Miller",
			"Jerrie Mock's",
			"Jacqueline Cochran"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the rarest M&M color?",
		"answer": "Brown",
		"options": ["Brown", "Green", "Blue", "Yellow"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What was the first soft drink that went to space?",
		"answer": "Coca Cola",
		"options": ["Coca Cola", "Pepsi", "Fanta", "Dr Pepper"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What part of the atom has no electric charge?",
		"answer": "neutron",
		"options": ["neutron", "proton", "electron", "nucleus"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the symbol for potassium?",
		"answer": "K",
		"options": ["K", "X", "S", "H"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which planet is the hottest in the solar system?",
		"answer": "Venus",
		"options": ["Venus", "Mercury", "Earth", "Jupiter"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many molecules of oxygen does ozone have?",
		"answer": "3",
		"options": ["3", "2", "4", "12"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which natural disaster is measured with a Richter scale?",
		"answer": "earthquake",
		"options": ["earthquake", "hurricane", "tornado", "drought"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is Hawkeye's real name?",
		"answer": "Clint Barton",
		"options": ["Clint Barton", "Tony Stark", "Peter Parker", "Steve Rogers"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many films did Sean Connery play James Bond in?",
		"answer": "7",
		"options": ["7", "3", "5", "1"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which auto brand was the first to offer seat belts?",
		"answer": "Nash Motors",
		"options": ["Nash Motors", "Ford", "Toyota", "BMW"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Bill Gates is the founder of which company?",
		"answer": "Microsoft",
		"options": ["Microsoft", "Google", "Apple", "Samsung"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Richard Branson is the owner of which airline?",
		"answer": "Virgin Atlantic",
		"options": [
			"Virgin Atlantic",
			"United Airlines",
			"American Airlines",
			"Spirit Airlines"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "What was X's (Twitter's) original name?",
		"answer": "twttr",
		"options": ["twttr", "Birdie", "Hoot", "tweeter"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the most used programming language according to Stack Overflow?",
		"answer": "JavaScript",
		"options": ["JavaScript", "Go", "Java", "Rust"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many Lord of the Rings films are there?",
		"answer": "3",
		"options": ["3", "1", "5", "4"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What president was a licensed bartender?",
		"answer": "Abraham Lincoln",
		"options": [
			"Abraham Lincoln",
			"George Washington",
			"Donald Trump",
			"Ulysses S. Grant"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "What year was the first Barbie doll released?",
		"answer": "1959",
		"options": ["1959", "2000", "2015", "1899"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which country gives students the longest summer holiday?",
		"answer": "Italy",
		"options": ["Italy", "America", "France", "Spain"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which blood type is a universal donor?",
		"answer": "O-",
		"options": ["O-", "O+", "A+", "B-"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the largest bone in the human body?",
		"answer": "femur",
		"options": ["femur", "humerus", "tibia", "skull"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many colors are in a rainbow?",
		"answer": "7",
		"options": ["7", "8", "10", "6"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many planets make up the solar system?",
		"answer": "8",
		"options": ["8", "6", "7", "5"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many pounds are in a ton?",
		"answer": "2,000",
		"options": ["2,000", "1,000", "1,760", "1,050"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What musician was awarded the first gold record?",
		"answer": "Perry Como",
		"options": [
			"Perry Como",
			"Elvis Presley",
			"Jimi Hendrix",
			"Prince Rogers Nelson"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "What year did MTV launch?",
		"answer": "1981",
		"options": ["1981", "1970", "1999", "1993"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What country does \"The Jungle Book\" take place in?",
		"answer": "India",
		"options": ["India", "South Africa", "Pakistan", "Arabia"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the Grinch's dog's name?",
		"answer": "Max",
		"options": ["Max", "Oliver", "Spot", "Simba"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the name of Boba Fett's ship in \"Star Wars\"?",
		"answer": "Slave 1",
		"options": [
			"Slave 1",
			"Millennium Falcon",
			"Home One",
			"Imperial Star Destroyer"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was the first Disney princess?",
		"answer": "Snow White",
		"options": ["Snow White", "Beauty", "Cinderella", "Moana"]
	},
	{
		"question": "In \"Star Wars,\" who built C-3P0?",
		"answer": "Anakin Skywalker",
		"options": [
			"Anakin Skywalker",
			"Luke Skywalker",
			"Darth Vader",
			"Obi-Wan Kenobi"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many ghosts show up in \"A Christmas Carol\"?",
		"answer": "4",
		"options": ["4", "3", "10", "1"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Who is the villain in \"Peter Pan\"?",
		"answer": "Captain Hook",
		"options": ["Captain Hook", "Scar", "Cruella de Vil", "Ursula"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which city is “101 Dalmatians” set in?",
		"answer": "London",
		"options": ["London", "New York City", "Orlando", "Sydney"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Play-Doh was originally invented for what purpose?",
		"answer": "cleaning wallpaper",
		"options": ["cleaning wallpaper", "cooking", "ironing", "sculpting"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What game is generally considered to have ushered in the video game era?",
		"answer": "Pong",
		"options": ["Pong", "Space Invaders", "Pac-Man", "Spacewar!"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What toy is created by mixing silicone oil and boric acid?",
		"answer": "Silly Putty",
		"options": ["Silly Putty", "Play-Doh", "Finger Paints", "Crayola Crayons"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which famous soft drink company was founded in 1892?",
		"answer": "Coca Cola",
		"options": ["Coca Cola", "Sprite", "Dr Pepper", "Pepsi"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is \"rotisserie\" food cooked on?",
		"answer": "a spit",
		"options": ["a spit", "a barbecue", "a fryer", "a stove"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the most expensive spice (by weight) in the world?",
		"answer": "saffron",
		"options": [
			"saffron",
			"black pepper",
			"vanilla bean",
			"mahleb",
			"fennel pollen"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "What nutrient comes from meat, eggs, and fish?",
		"answer": "protein",
		"options": ["protein", "fiber", "vitamins", "minerals"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the smallest planet in our solar system?",
		"answer": "Mercury",
		"options": ["Mercury", "Earth", "Mars", "Saturn"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the largest planet in our solar system?",
		"answer": "Jupiter",
		"options": ["Jupiter", "Earth", "Uranus", "Neptune"]
	},
	{
		"question": "The moon called Titan orbits which planet?",
		"answer": "Saturn",
		"options": ["Saturn", "Jupiter", "Venus", "Mars"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which is the brightest planet in the night's sky?",
		"answer": "Venus",
		"options": ["Venus", "Mars", "Mercury", "Neptune"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many of our planets can be seen without a telescope?",
		"answer": "5",
		"options": ["5", "7", "2", "1"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which planet has the most moons?",
		"answer": "Saturn",
		"options": ["Saturn", "Jupiter", "Neptune", "Mercury"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which planet has the fastest rotation?",
		"answer": "Jupiter",
		"options": ["Jupiter", "Earth", "Venus", "Uranus"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which planet is known as the Morning Star and Evening Star?",
		"answer": "Venus",
		"options": ["Venus", "Saturn", "Mercury", "Uranus"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which planet spins backward relative to the others?",
		"answer": "Venus",
		"options": ["Venus", "Neptune", "Uranus", "Mars"]
	},
	{
		"question": "The atmosphere protects the earth from radiation.",
		"answer": "true",
		"options": ["true", "false"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Mercury has no moons.",
		"answer": "true",
		"options": ["true", "false"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Neptune is the closest planet to the sun.",
		"answer": "false",
		"options": ["false", "true"]
	},
	{
		"question": "It takes a sloth two weeks to digest a meal.",
		"answer": "true",
		"options": ["true", "false"]
	},
	{
		"question": "When exiting a cave, bats always go in the direction of the wind.",
		"answer": "false",
		"options": ["false", "true"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What animals have the thickest fur of any mammals?",
		"answer": "sea otters",
		"options": ["sea otters", "dogs", "mice", "racoons"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Bats are blind.",
		"answer": "false",
		"options": ["false", "true"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What mythical creature is Scotland's national animal?",
		"answer": "Unicorn",
		"options": ["Unicorn", "Dragon", "Goblin", "Griffin"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What animal has the highest blood pressure?",
		"answer": "giraffe",
		"options": ["giraffe", "ostrich", "hamster", "octopus"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What mammal has the most powerful bite?",
		"answer": "hippopotamus",
		"options": ["hippopotamus", "lion", "alligator", "blue whale"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the closest living relative to the T-rex?",
		"answer": "chicken",
		"options": ["chicken", "gecko", "deer", "pig"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the deadliest creature in the world?",
		"answer": "mosquito",
		"options": ["mosquito", "tick", "lion", "shark"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many legs does a lobster have?",
		"answer": "10",
		"options": ["10", "12", "6", "4"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What was the name of the first electronic general-purpose computer?",
		"answer": "ENIAC",
		"options": ["ENIAC", "Colossus Mark 1", "Macintosh 128K", "ABC"]
	},
	{
		"question": "One kilobyte is equal to how many bytes?",
		"answer": "1,024",
		"options": ["1,024", "1,000", "10,000", "1,540"]
	},
	{
		"question": "In what year was the Nintendo 64 officially released?",
		"answer": "1996",
		"options": ["1996", "1964", "2001", "1991"]
	},
	{
		"question": "RAM stands for \"Random Access Memory\".",
		"answer": "true",
		"options": ["true", "false"]
	},
	{
		"question": "In what year was the iPhone first released?",
		"answer": "2007",
		"options": ["2007", "2001", "2010", "1990"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the name of the main protagonist in the Legend of Zelda series of video games?",
		"answer": "Link",
		"options": ["Link", "Zelda", "Waluigi", "Mario"]
	},
	{
		"question": "NES stands for \"Nintendo Emulating System\".",
		"answer": "false",
		"options": ["true", "false"]
	},
	{
		"question": "SQL in database programming stands for \"Superlative Query Language\".",
		"answer": "false",
		"options": ["true", "false"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What year was Facebook founded?",
		"answer": "2004",
		"options": ["2004", "2010", "1999", "2007"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Steve Jobs, Steve Wozniak, and Ronald Wayne founded what company in 1976?",
		"answer": "Apple",
		"options": ["Apple", "Microsoft", "Google", "Samsung"]
	},
	{
		"question": "HTML and CSS are computer languages used to create what?",
		"answer": "websites",
		"options": ["websites", "mobile apps", "desktop apps", "games"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Ariana Grande got her start on what kids TV show?",
		"answer": "Victorious",
		"options": ["Victorious", "Sam & Cat", "PAW Patrol", "Arthur"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was the first winner of The Masked Singer?",
		"answer": "T-Pain",
		"options": ["T-Pain", "Amber Riley", "LeAnn Rimes", "Wayne Brady"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which entrepreneur named his son X Æ A-12?",
		"answer": "Elon Musk",
		"options": ["Elon Musk", "Bill Gates", "Mark Zuckerberg", "Warren Buffett"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What was the name of Meghan Markle's lifestyle blog before she married into the royal family?",
		"answer": "The Tig",
		"options": ["The Tig", "Markle's Blog", "Miss Markle", "Rug Road"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What year was YouTube founded?",
		"answer": "2005",
		"options": ["2005", "2008", "2001", "2010"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was the first president of the United States?",
		"answer": "George Washington",
		"options": ["George Washington", "Abraham Lincoln", "James Monroe", "Thomas Jefferson"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Native to the Caribbean, what kind of animal is a Mountain Chicken?",
		"answer": "frog",
		"options": ["frog", "goat", "duck", "catfish"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What bird has eyes bigger than its brain?",
		"answer": "ostrich",
		"options": ["ostrich", "hummingbird", "swallow", "blue jay"]
	}
]